SABO JISE

WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

Music & Worship Director | Maple Ridge Community Church

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019 | Maple Ridge, BC

- Established a consistent and cohesive worship culture in a congregation of five hundred people.
- Trained and equipped seven sound techs and media operators in the competent use of sound systems and media equipment.
- Created and established consistent and clear expectations and standards for leaders, team, and ministry members

Training Instructor | Youth With A Mission

Dec 2005 - 2017 | Perth, Australia

- Co-designed and led the development of the core curriculum for the training of musicians through modern and ethnomusicology.
- Organized and led a team of 10-15 musicians each year, going on tours overseas for a cross-cultural music experience working with local musicians.

Music Ministry Leader | Youth With A Mission

Jan 2014 - 2018 | Perth, Australia

- Accountable for mentoring and empowering a diverse team of career musicians in the development of their professional skills such as networking, resource management, music production, and marketing.
- Formed and managed a funk-Rock band of 5 musicians, cultivating technical skills in performance, team dynamic and character development

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma Candidate, Web Development

May 2020 - Sept 2020 | Vancouver, BC

Shaw Academy | Diploma, Mobile App Development

Sept2017 - Jan 2018 | Dublin County, Dublin (online)

PROJECTS

Click **HERE** to View Projects

sajiyoonline@gmail.com 778-512-8464 linkedin.com/in/sabojise/ github.com/Sabzs

SKILLS

Front-End: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Document Object Model (DOM) APIs

Back- End: Node.js, Express.js, Web APIs, User Authentication, Oauth

Databases: MySQL **ORMs:** Sequelize **Testing:** Jest, Enzyme

Deployment & Development Tools:

Heroku, GitHub, WebPack

PROFILE

My dream is to contribute to a better world through web development and technology. I am passionate about the ability to create and bring imaginations to life through visual representation, creating something unique that people can feel, interact with, and work with. I believe that my musical background will strengthen me in this career as it has provided me with keen attention to detail, the ability to persevere and refine until excellence is achieved, a strong ability to be self-disciplined, and the skill to coordinate multiple tasks at once. I embrace challenges, offer diverse experiences, and am an agile learner.